[
    {
        "categoria":"Nivel 1",
        "pregunta": "Hello",
        "respuesta": "Hola",
        "incorrecta1": "Adiós",
        "incorrecta2": "Chau",
        "incorrecta3": "Salud\r"
    },
    {
        "categoria":"Nivel 1",
        "pregunta": "Water",
        "respuesta": "Agua",
        "incorrecta1": "Fuego",
        "incorrecta2": "Cielo",
        "incorrecta3": "Azul\r"
    },
    {
        "categoria":"Nivel 1",
        "pregunta": "Cat",
        "respuesta": "Gato",
        "incorrecta1": "Perro",
        "incorrecta2": "Tumba",
        "incorrecta3": "Celular\r"
    },
    {
        "categoria":"Nivel 1",
        "pregunta": "Dog",
        "respuesta": "Perro",
        "incorrecta1": "Pájaro",
        "incorrecta2": "Oceáno",
        "incorrecta3": "Casa\r"
    },
    {
        "categoria":"Nivel 1",
        "pregunta": "House",
        "respuesta": "Casa",
        "incorrecta1": "Ciudad",
        "incorrecta2": "Pelota",
        "incorrecta3": "Mesa\r"
    },
    {
        "categoria":"Nivel 1",
        "pregunta": "Blue",
        "respuesta": "Azul",
        "incorrecta1": "Blanco",
        "incorrecta2": "Rojo",
        "incorrecta3": "Amarillo\r"
    },
    {
        "categoria":"Nivel 1",
        "pregunta": "Four",
        "respuesta": "Cuatro",
        "incorrecta1": "Diez",
        "incorrecta2": "Uno",
        "incorrecta3": "Cinco\r"
    },
    {
        "categoria":"Nivel 1",
        "pregunta": "White",
        "respuesta": "Blanco",
        "incorrecta1": "Negro",
        "incorrecta2": "Azul",
        "incorrecta3": "Morado\r"
    },
    {
        "categoria":"Nivel 1",
        "pregunta": "Sun",
        "respuesta": "Sol",
        "incorrecta1": "Cielo",
        "incorrecta2": "Brazo",
        "incorrecta3": "Cabeza\r"
    },
    {
        "categoria":"Nivel 1",
        "pregunta": "Black",
        "respuesta": "Negro",
        "incorrecta1": "Rojo",
        "incorrecta2": "Celeste",
        "incorrecta3": "Azul\r"
    }
]